GT Booster’s Privacy Policy informs you of how we collect, use and share your personal data, and our privacy practices.
=======================================================================================================================

* Solutions

#### Network Visibility & Intelligence

[

ARK Engine

AI visibility solution that gives context to your traffic intelligence.](https://www.gtbooster.com/ark-engine)

#### Network Traffic Management

[

AIFlow

PC software that empowers you with traffic monitoring and management.](https://www.gtbooster.com/aiflow)[

ARK AI QoE

Smart and dynamic AI QoE that greatly enhances router performance.](https://www.gtbooster.com/ark-ai-qoe)[

ARK Parental Control

Ever-evolving content filtering feature to protect children 24/7.](https://www.gtbooster.com/ark-parental-control)

#### Network Acceleration Service

[

GT Net

A smart pathfinder for lowest latencies and best connections.](https://www.gtbooster.com/gt-net)

* [Solutions](javascript:void(0);)
    
    #### Network Visibility & Intelligence

    #### Network Traffic Management

    #### Network Acceleration Service

GT Booster Privacy Policy
-------------------------

Last updated: 27 June 2023. These Terms replace and supersede all prior versions.  
  
**IMPORTANT! PLEASE READ CAREFULLY.**  
  
GT Booster Corporation, its subsidiaries and its affiliated companies ("**GT Booster**", "**we/our/us**") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We communicate our privacy and security guidelines to our employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.  
  
Our Privacy Policy, together with any privacy-related notices or statements that contain supplementary information in connection with our Services and Software (as defined in our [Terms of Use](https://www.gtbooster.com/legal/terms)) you are using (collectively, "**Privacy Policy**"), informs you of how we collect, use and share your personal data, the choices you can make, the privacy rights you can exercise in relation to your personal data, and other privacy practices.  
  
We define personal data in accordance to guidelines stipulated by the General Data Protection Regulation ("**GDPR**") – meaning that all data that directly or reasonably used to identify you is considered personal data. Also in accordance with GDPR and for the purposes of this document, data that has been aggregated and anonymized does not constitute personal data.  
  
This Privacy Policy does not apply to any personal data we process on behalf of our business partners when we provide services. The contracts we have with our business partners control how we process your personal data in this context. In such circumstances, we suggest that you first contact our business partner if you have questions about your personal data, and, if needed, we will provide assistance to our partner in responding to your inquiries.  

### 1\. Personal Data We May Collect From You

The personal data GT Booster collects from you depends on the context of your interactions with us, the choices you make (such as Cookie Settings), and your prior consent. We strive to collect only the personal data that are necessary to provide our Services and Software. We may collect a variety of the following information:

* **Contact Information.** Data such as personal and/or business name, phone number, email address, mailing address, country or region, or other contact information.
* **Account and Credentials Information.** Your GT Booster account-related data, including account ID, password, password hints, date of birth, other security information required for authentication and access, and support history.
* **Payment and Transaction Information.** Data necessary for processing payments and preventing fraud, including method of payment, billing address, purchase or transaction information and other related billing or order information.
* **Device Data.** We collect information about your device, such as operating system, serial number, model number, device manufacturer, and other relevant information that varies by device.
* **Application and Usage Data.** We collect information related to our Services and Software such as IP address, software versions, performance data, diagnostic data, and other relevant data.
* **Website Data.** We use cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies to collect data regarding how you interact with our websites in order to improve our content quality. For more information, please refer to section 8 (Cookies and Similar Technologies).
* **Other Information You Provide to Us.** We may collect other information provided by you such as the content of your interactions with our customer support or social media channels. We may also provide social media features that enable you to share information with your social networks that may result in the sharing of information about you.

### 2\. Personal Data We MAY Receive From Other Sources

GT Booster may receive personal data about you from other individuals, from businesses or third parties acting at your direction, from our partners who assist us in security and fraud prevention or work with us to provide our Services and Software, and from other lawful sources.

* **Individuals.** GT Booster may collect data about you from other individuals. For example, if that individual has purchased our Services or Software on your behalf.
* **At Your Direction.** You may direct other individuals or third parties to share data with GT Booster. For example, you may direct social media providers to share information about your account if you choose to create your GT Booster account using your social media account.
* **GT Booster Partners and Service Providers.** We may also validate the information you provide. For example, when processing a purchase order using a third party service provider to handle payment.

### 3\. How We Use Personal Data

GT Booster uses personal data to enable the functionality of our Services and Software, to process transactions, for security and fraud prevention, to comply with law, and, most importantly, to better serve and communicate with you. We may also use personal data for other purposes with your consent, when it's in our legitimate interests or when we have a valid legal basis to do so. We only retain the personal data for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, including as described in this Privacy Policy or in our other service-specific documents, or as required by law.

* **To Provide Services and Software.** GT Booster collects personal data necessary to ensure the functionality of our Services and Software. This data may also be used to improve our offerings (including auditing or data analysis), to provide services and support, or for troubleshooting.
* **Process Payment and Orders.** Assisting you in completing transactions and orders of our Services and Software, administering your account, processing payments and other related services.
* **Security and Fraud Prevention.** To maintain the integrity and security of our Services and Software and prevent security threats, fraud or other criminal or malicious activity that might compromise your information.
* **Compliance with Law.** To comply with applicable laws, regulations, court orders, or lawful governmental requests.
* **Offer a Personalized Experience.** In accordance with your privacy preferences, we may use a combination of data collected to enable us to provide personalized services, communication or offerings on a variety of platforms, and to study the effectiveness of advertising and marketing campaigns.
* **Communication.** To communicate with you about GT Booster Services and Software, including responding to your inquiries or requests, service completion or warranty-related communications, or communications required by law or applicable corporate updates related to mergers, acquisitions, or divestitures.

### 4\. How We Share Personal Data

We may share personal data with our affiliated companies, third party service providers who act on our behalf, our partners, or others for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, and, when applicable, only with the appropriate contractual obligations in place.

* **Service Providers.** We may engage third party service providers to handle certain aspects of our business on our behalf, such as processing or storing data (including personal data), processing payment, fraud prevention services, and customer support among others. GT Booster service providers are obligated or required to handle personal data consistent with this Privacy Policy and according to our instructions. They cannot use the personal data we share for their own purposes and must delete or return the personal data once they've fulfilled our request.
* **GT Booster Partners**  
    We may integrate our Software and Services into our third-party partner's products. If you purchase products that bundle our Software and Services as part of our partner's product offering, we create a customer ID that is unique to you and the product's manufacturer. In such cases, we may share information related to your usage of the products or our Services and Software to the respective partner in order to improve your user experience.
* **Others.** We may also share your information:
    1. With your consent or at your direction;
    2. Disclosure is necessary or appropriate for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance;
    3. If there is a lawful basis for doing so;
    4. If we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or to protect our operations or users;
    5. If we merge or are acquired by another company, sell a GT Booster website, app, or business unit, or if all or a substantial portion of our assets are acquired by another company;
    6. In the event of a reorganization.

### 5\. International Data Transfers

GT Booster, as well as our third party service providers and partners, operate around the world. This means that when we collect your personal data, we may transfer the data to adequate countries other than the country in which you reside; these transfers are permitted and legal under the GDPR. These countries may have different data protection laws to the laws of your country. Whenever GT Booster transfers personal data beyond the country of origin, we will do so in accordance with all applicable local privacy laws and regulations.  
  
When transferring personal data originating in the European Economic Area ("**EEA**") to a GT Booster entity, third party service providers or partners located in a country that does not have an "adequate level of protection" as determined by the European Commission, we do so on the basis of the European Commission's [Standard Contractual Clauses](https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc_en).  
  
As to the processing of personal data relating to individuals in China outside of China, it will be done in compliance with local laws, including the Personal Information Protection Law.

### 6\. Children's Privacy

GT Booster understands the importance of safeguarding the personal data of children. We define children as individuals under the age of 16 or the equivalent age as specified by law in your jurisdiction. Unless otherwise stated for a specific Service or Software, GT Booster Services and Software are made for the general public. We do not knowingly collect data from children as defined by local law without the previous consent of their parents or legal guardians or as otherwise permitted by applicable law. If you believe that we may have collected personal information from a minor without the requisite consent, please contact us at [dpo@gtbooster.com](mailto:dpo@gtbooster.com) and we will investigate and address the issue.  
  
If we learn that a child's personal data was collected without appropriate authorization, it will be deleted as soon as reasonably possible.

### 7\. Exercising Your Rights

GT Booster respects your privacy rights. Under the law of some jurisdictions, you may have the data protection rights as below. To exercise your rights, please contact our Data Protection Officer directly at [dpo@gtbooster.com.](mailto:dpo@gtbooster.com) Upon receipt of your email, our Data Protection Officer will review and respond to you within 14 days. In some cases, we may require additional information or let you know that we need additional time to respond.

* Ask us for a copy of any personal data that you have provided to us or that we maintain about you and to request an explanation about the processing;
* Withdraw any consent previously granted for the processing of your personal information;
* Correct, amend, anonymize or delete your personal data;
* Obtain the personal data you provided with your consent or in connection with a contract in a structured, readable format and to ask us to transfer this data to another data controller;
* Object to the processing of your personal data;
* Opt-out of marketing communication emails (click the "unsubscribe" or "opt-out" link in the emails directly) or other forms of marketing.

In certain cases, these rights may be limited – for example, if fulfilling your request would reveal personal data about another person, if you ask us to delete information which we are required by law to keep or if the request would otherwise undermine other legitimate uses of the data. Please note that withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than the consent. If we are unable to resolve your concerns, you may lodge a complaint with the data protection authorities handling data protection in your country or region.  
  
We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights and choices, but please note some of the functionality and features available in our Services and Software depend on the personal data you make available to us. As a result, some functionality and features available in our Services and Software may change or no longer be available to you according to your choices.

### 8\. Cookies and Similar Technologies

GT Booster and our third party partners use cookies (cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer, tablet, mobile phone or other devices when you visit or interact with a website) and other similar technologies, such as web beacons, for various purposes such as making the websites function properly, keeping our websites and services secure, analyzing website performance, and most importantly, providing you with a better and more personalized experience.  
  
The cookies we generally use fit into one of the categories below:

* **Strictly Necessary Cookies.** These cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.
* **Functional Cookies.** These cookies enable the website to provide enhanced functionality and personalization. They may be set by us or by third party providers whose services we have added to our pages. If you do not allow these cookies then some or all of these services may not function properly.
* **Performance Cookies.** These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.
* **Targeting Cookies.** These cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. They do not store directly personal information, but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.
* **Social Media Cookies.** These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to the site to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit. If you do not allow these cookies you may not be able to use or see these sharing tools.

You may choose to block some types of cookies, however, please note that disabling some types of cookies may prevent you from being able to access certain parts of our Services. Also, note that changing your cookie preferences will not delete or overwrite existing cookies. You will need to go to your browser settings to configure or delete them. Click on the links below for more information on how to access cookie settings for some of the most common and widely-used browsers.

GT Booster and our service providers may implement web beacons (often a transparent graphic pixel GIF or PNG image) and other technologies on websites or in emails to measure the effectiveness of campaigns or promotions. We may use the information, such as page visits, email open rate, and link clicks to further improve our Services.  
  
Many browsers have a "Do Not Track" feature that allows you to tell websites you do not want to have your online activities tracked. Currently, there is no industry agreed upon standard on how companies should respond to the "Do Not Track" signals, and so accordingly, our Services do not currently recognize or respond to these signals.

### 9\. California Privacy Rights

We do not monetize your personal information except to the extent permitted under California law. If you are a California resident, subject to certain limits under California law, you have the right to:

* Request an explanation for the collection and processing of your personal information;
* Access, request and receive the personal information we have collected in a portable manner;
* Object to having your personal data sold, as defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act ("**CCPA**");
* Request for deletion of your personal data (with exceptions as defined by the CCPA).

We do not discriminate against you if you choose to exercise these rights. To exercise your rights, please contact our Data Protection Officer directly at [dpo@gtbooster.com.](mailto:dpo@gtbooster.com) Upon receipt of your email, our Data Protection Officer will review and respond to you within 14 days. In some cases, we may require additional information or let you know that we need additional time to respond.

### 10\. Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time to accommodate new technologies, privacy practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes. The revised policy will be posted here, and the "last updated" date at the top of the document will be updated with each revision. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will become effective immediately once posted.  
  
If the changes are material or significant, we may use reasonable efforts to notify you through other means, such as posting a notice at least seven days in advance on our website and contacting you directly if we have your information on file. We will also obtain your consent where required by applicable law. We encourage you to periodically review our Privacy Policy to stay informed of our privacy practices.

### 11\. Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about GT Booster's Privacy Policy or privacy practices, would like to exercise your privacy rights as described in section 7 (Exercising Your Rights), or would like to submit a privacy-related complaint, please contact our Data Protection Officer at [dpo@gtbooster.com.](mailto:dpo@gtbooster.com) All communications will be treated confidentially. Upon receipt of your email, our Data Protection Officer will review and respond to you within 14 days. In some cases, we may require additional information or let you know that we need additional time to respond.

20F-3, No. 118, Ciyun Rd. East Dist., Hsinchu City 300, Taiwan (R.O.C.)  
Copyright © 2024 GT Booster Inc. All rights reserved.

###### Company

* News (Coming Soon)

###### Solutions

20F-3, No. 118, Ciyun Rd. East Dist., Hsinchu City 300, Taiwan (R.O.C.)  
  
© 2024 GT Booster Inc. All rights reserved.
